CARMEN ZENG

7368-203 Royal Oak Ave | 604-719-2319 | Carmenzeng17@gmail.com

Skills Summary

I am a hardworking and reliable high school student with a strong interest in pursuing business and computer science. I have strong leadership skills and strive to contribute my valuable skills with ambition. I have gained large amounts of experience being the public relations and marketing director as well as a school ambassador lead of a youth non-profit organization supporting girls in business. Such includes leading my department, organizing and advertising events, graphic design and marketing, holding meetings and managing social media accounts as well as facilitating, promoting their growth.

Education

Moscrop Secondary School | 2018-2023

- Above 3.7 GPA throughout high school
- Honour roll certificate 2018-now
- Work habits certificate 2018-now
- Volunteer services certificate 2018-2020

Experience

Whatever Tea

Barista | Aug 2020-Dec 2021

- This was a long-term job I was committed to; during which I learned many important skills including communication skills in the workplace, how to work in a team, leadership skills and working under pressure
- I am a versatile worker and can quickly learn new positions such as cashier and preparation when needed
- I can quickly adapt to my environment

Burnaby Hospice Society Thrift Store

Volunteer | Jun 2022- Sept 2022

- Through this experience I learned valuable skills of teamwork, communication and problem solving
- I gained a sense of community and cooperation within the team and my supervisors

Clubs and organizations

EMGirls organization

Public relations director/ambassador/graphic designer | Sept 2022-now

EMGirls is a nonprofit organization led by girls in high school with a passion for pursuing business, aiming to empower girls and provide them with resources and support. Together, with the EMGirls executive team and leading the public relations department, I have organized events connecting youth to mentors in the business field and supported local female entrepreneurs. My role in the organization has allowed me to take on more responsibilities, as well as strengthen my leadership and management skills. In the months I have been a part of EMGirls, I have contributed over 400 minutes.

Deer Lake Youth Council

Volunteer | Sept 2022-now

The Deer Lake Youth Council is the local council run by youth in high school under the guidance of MLA Anne Kang. The council allows students to take initiative by organizing and volunteering for local events. Following my initial application, I have volunteered at several events, including a food drive for the local temple and the Burnaby bubble tea festival. Through these experiences I have become more connected to the community and developed stronger teamwork skills.

Truth and Reconciliation committee

Student voice | Sept 2022-now

The Truth and Reconciliation committee was created by teachers to continue the learning and reflecting of Indigenous history within the school community. As a chosen student voice and active member, I have spoken at an assembly, created a display case and participated in other activities to spread awareness educate my peers. Through these meaningful experiences I have gained valuable knowledge and a sense of responsibility regarding myself and others.

Ethics bowl club

Member | Sept 2022-now

The ethics bowl club encourages students to take initiative of their learning to educate themselves and engage in deep discussions regarding real world problems. Often students are required to think of solutions for complicated issues and weigh their advantages and disadvantages. I have participated in one competition thus far; in return I was able to learn so much from different perspectives and open my mind to new ideas. Through experience, the public speaking and unpredictable elements of the competition allowed me to build confidence in myself.

School clubs (executive positions)

Badminton team

Coaches' assistant | 2019-2022 season

Moscrop R.A.C.E club

Social media executive | Sept 2021- Jun 2022

Panther support club

Operations and social media executive | Sept 2022-now

Moscrop coding club

Social media executive | Sept 2022-now

Moscrop business club

Operations executive | Sept 2022-now